testerkorea.com 2018-11-11

# TesterKorea | Korea Cosmetics | Korean Beauty Products | K-Beauty | Global Online Shop

    This English translation is provided for your reference purposes only, and is not legally binding. 
    Only a Korean version of the privacy policy is legally binding.
    
    1. Collection and Use of Personal Information
    
    A. We collect personal information to verify the identity of our customer and confirm his or her intent 
    to use our services to provide optimal custom-designed services to the customer. We collect only the
    minimum information necessary to help a customer to use our services, when the customer first signs 
    up to be a member. We may additionally collect information necessary for payment, delivery of goods and 
    services, refund and the like, following customer’s use of our services.
    
    B. We do not use the personal information for any purpose other than that set forth herein or disclose 
    such information to any third party without the consent of the customer.
    
    C. We collect and use personal information for the following purposes described below. However, we may, 
    after notification, collect a resident registration number if it is inevitable to collect and store it 
    and bank account information pursuant to applicable laws and regulations (including without limitation,
    the Framework Act of National Tax and the Electronic Financial Transactions Act), and mobile phone 
    number information if it is inevitable to collect and store it for the settlement of payment through the 
    small-sum settlement on using the mobile phone, etc..
    1) Name, E-mail address (Login ID), telephone number, address, and E-mail address of recipient: for 
    communications to facilitate transactions, confirm his/her intent, handle complaints, give updates on 
    services and notifications, etc.
    2) The following information may be collected from users who use value-added services and customized 
    services or enter sweepstakes.
    - If the user agrees to the collection of additional personal information.
    3) Other: In the course of your using our services or transaction processing, the following information 
    may be automatically generated and collected: 
    - IP address, date and time of visit, records of use of our services: to prevent unauthorized use and 
    misuse
    
    D. In the case of collecting personal information of a customer, the Company will collect the 
    information with his/her consent, and will not collect information on race, origin, legal domicile of 
    origin, religion, political disposition, criminal records, health condition and other information 
    likely to infringe on the fundamental rights of customers, unless upon the consent of the relevant 
    individual or required by law.
    
    E. The Company only allows people of age 14 and up to register as members, and as a general rule, it 
    does not collect information of people under the age of 14, for the collection of whose information is 
    required the consent of their legal guardians. However, the company may collect and use the personal 
    information of people under the age of 14 if their legal guardian consents.
    
    F. We may collect personal information in the following manner:
    1) collection on/through the Company’s homepage, in writing, by facsimile, by phone, through your 
    contacting a customer center, and through your participating in an event; and
    2) automatic collection through tools to collect generated information
    
    2. Provision and Sharing of Personal Information to or with a Third Party
    
    A. We will use customers’ personal information only for the purposes and within the scope of use 
    identified in the “Collection and Use of Personal Information” Section above. We will not use 
    the personal information beyond such scope without the prior consent of the relevant individual, 
    and as a general rule, we will not provide the information to any third party, except as set out below.
    1) if the relevant individual consents, in advance, to the disclosure or provision to a third party; or
    2) if required by law, or if requested by the law enforcement or competent authority pursuant to the 
    procedures and methods of due process prescribed by applicable laws and regulations for the purpose of 
    a criminal or other investigation.
    
    B. If placement of an order or payment is made for a transaction through services provided by the 
    Company, we may provide the other party thereto with relevant information to help such other party to 
    carry out the transaction (including but not limited to delivery), or to facilitate communications 
    between the parties thereto (including but not limited to consultation), but in any event only to the 
    extent necessary.
    
    C. If otherwise necessary to provide personal information to a third party, we may provide or share 
    personal information to or with a third party upon consent from customers through due process. The 
    recipients to which we provide the personal information with consent from customers, and the purposes 
    of their uses are set out below.
    
    3. Outsourcing of Processing of Personal Information
    
    A. We may outsource personal information processing services to third party service providers to 
    facilitate and improve our services.
    
    B. In relation to processing of personal information, we outsource such tasks as set out below to 
    third-party service providers and, when executing outsourcing contracts with them, take measures 
    necessary to ensure security in the management of personal information. Further, information processed 
    through outsourcing arrangements is limited to the minimum information necessary to facilitate 
    provision of our services. Our third-party service providers for the processing of personal information 
    of our customers and the purposes of outsourcing are set out below.
    
    Third-party Service Providers	Outsourced Tasks
    Post Office	International delivery
    Worldwide Courier service	International delivery
    DHL	International delivery
    
    4. Duration of Retention and Use of Personal Information and Destruction
    
    As a general rule, the Company retains and uses customer’s personal information for the notified and 
    agreed durations and once the purposes of collection and use of the personal information are achieved, 
    it is without delay destroyed (provided, however, that the personal information will be destroyed after 
    two (2) months from the date of termination of a shopping service user agreement (“User Agreement”) 
    to prevent re-registration during the re-registration probation period). Further, the following 
    information may be retained for such duration for such reasons as set out below:
    
    A. Retention pursuant to applicable laws and policies of the Company
    If required to retain personal information pursuant to applicable laws, including without limitation 
    the Commercial Code, we retain user’s personal information for such duration as prescribed thereby, 
    in which case the Company will use the information solely for the purposes of retention, and applicable 
    durations of retention are set out below.
    1) Records on contracts or withdrawal of offers and the like
    - Reasons for retention: Article 6 of the e-Commerce Act; and Article 6 of the Enforcement Ordinance 
    thereof
    - Duration of Retention: 5 years
    2) Records on payment settlement and supply of goods, etc.
    - Reasons for retention: Article 6 of the e-Commerce Act; and Article 6 of the Enforcement Ordinance 
    thereof
    - Duration of Retention: 5 years
    3) Records on processing of customer disputes and complaints
    - Reasons for retention: Article 6 of the e-Commerce Act; and Article 6 of the Enforcement Ordinance 
    thereof
    - Duration of Retention: 3 years
    4) Records on access
    - Reasons for retention: Article 15-2 of the Communications Secrecy Protection Act; and Article 41 of 
    the Enforcement Ordinance thereof
    - Duration of Retention: 3 months
    5) Records on misbehaviors in the use of services
    - Reasons for retention: Retention pursuant to the Company’s policies, such as, prohibition of 
    misbehaviors 
    - Duration of Retention: 5 years
    
    B. The duration of retention / use of collected personal information will start from when the User 
    Agreement is entered into (i.e., signing up for a membership) and end when the User Agreement is 
    terminated (including, but not limited to, applying for withdrawal from the membership, and 
    discretionary withdrawal/dismissal). 
    Further, in the case of termination of the User Agreement upon mutual agreement, the Company will 
    without delay destroy all of your personal information other than contained in materials required to 
    retain for a certain period for the afore-mentioned reasons for data retention, and will also instruct 
    its third-party service providers to destroy the personal information provided to them for the 
    outsourcing of data processing.
    
    5. Cookies
    
    A. Purpose of Use of Cookies
    1) We use cookies to save and find information about the members’ accounts in order to provide 
    personally customized services to the members. A cookie is a small text file of information about the 
    basic setting of a website, sent by the website’s web server to the web browser of a user of the 
    website, and it is stored in the hard disc of the computer used by you.
    2) We can provide you with particular customized services that can be possible only by use of cookies.
    3) We may use cookies to identify members and recognize them remaining in a log-in status.
    
    B. Installation and Operation/maintenance of Cookies and Refusal thereof 
    
    1) You have an option to accept or refuse installation of cookies. Therefore, you can choose the options 
    of your web browser to accept all cookies, to receive notice when cookies are installed, or to refuse 
    all cookies. 
    
    - How to enable/disable cookies on Internet Explorer 
    ＊ Click the Tools button, and then click Internet Options.
    ＊ Click the Privacy tab.
    ＊ Under Settings, move the slider to the top to block all cookies or to the bottom to allow all 
    cookies, and then click OK.
    
    2) However, if you refuse cookies, you may not be able to access certain services provided by the 
    Company that require cookies.
    
    6. Rights of Users
    
    A. You may at any time access, check or correct your registered personal information at the “
    Information Correction” page of TesterKorea. If you make a request for checking or correction of it 
    to our Privacy Officer in writing or by e-mail, we will take care of your request. If, however, your 
    name has been duly changed, or if your resident (business) registration number has been duly changed for 
    administrative reasons, then correction of such information may be exceptionally permissible. If 
    correction or removal is prohibited or restricted under applicable law or regulation, fulfillment of
    your request may be restricted. Further, if you request correction of your personal information, the 
    relevant personal information will not be used or provided until correction has been completed, unless 
    provision of the information is requested pursuant to any other applicable law or regulation. As for 
    information that was already provided to a third party, the third party will be notified of the results 
    of correction, so that the corrected information may apply as soon as the correction process is 
    complete.
    
    B. You may at any time request to stop handling of your personal information at TesterKorea; provided 
    thatin the following case, we may refuse to satisfy your request:
    1) if particularly prescribed by any law or regulation, or if the handling is inevitable to perform 
    obligations in compliance with applicable law or regulation;
    2) if there is apprehension that life/body of any other person may be harmed or that the property and 
    other interest of any other person may be unjustly infringed upon; or
    3) if, without handling the personal information, it is impossible to perform a contract with the 
    customer (such as a contract for provision of service), where the customer has not expressly made it 
    clear that he/she intends to terminate the contract.)
    
    C. You may at any time withdraw your consent to our collection, use, and provision of personal 
    information (whether provided at the sign-up process or otherwise). The consent can be withdrawn on the 
    web (by clicking “application for withdrawal from a membership” at TesterKorea), or by 
    contacting our Privacy Officer in writing, by phone, by email or otherwise. At your request, we will 
    take necessary measures to handle withdrawal requests without delay; provided that, if required to keep 
    in storage your personal information pursuant to applicable law, regulation or terms and conditions, 
    handling of your withdrawal request may be restricted. In such case, you must disclose your Member ID 
    and personally identifiable information to verify your identity. Upon withdrawal, your use of the 
    Service may be somewhat limited or the Service in part or wholly may be unavailable to you.
    
    7. Responsibilities of Users
    
    You have obligations to protect your own personal information, and we are in no event responsible for 
    any issues or problems arising out of the leak of personal information caused by your own negligence 
    (such as, transfer, lending or loss of your ID, Password, access medium, etc., leaving a PC without 
    logging out, and the like), inherent problems in Internet (such as, vulnerability of browsers, hacking 
    by use of such technology or method as cannot be prevented by security measures compliant with 
    applicable laws and regulations and as controllable despite of substantial care taken by the Company to 
    prevent the same) and the like, in each case, so long as it is not attributable to the Company.
    
    A. You should keep your personal information up-to-date, and are solely responsible for any accidents 
    arising out of your provision of inaccurate information.
    
    B. You are responsible to keep your ID, password etc. securely protected. You should not assign or lend 
    any of them to a third party. You have obligations to cooperate with the Company’s request to 
    change your passwords regularly for security purposes pursuant to the Policy.
    
    C. After using our services, you should log out from your account and close the web browser.
    
    D. You must comply with all laws and regulations concerning personal information, including but not 
    limited to the IC Network Act, the Personal Information Protection Act, and the Resident Registration 
    Act.
    
    8. Liability on Links to Other Web Sites
    
    We can provide you with links to another websites. However, this Policy is not applicable to such other 
    sites’ collection of personal information.
    
    9. Technical / Managerial Safeguards to Protect Personal Information
    
    In handling your personal information, we take the following technical/managerial safeguards to ensure 
    your personal information secure from loss, theft, leak, falsification or destruction:
    
    A. Encryption of Personal Information
    Your passwords will be, after one-way encryption, kept and managed, and only you who knows the 
    passwords can check and modify your passwords. We set rules on the generation of passwords so as to 
    prevent you from using your birthday, phone number, or any other numbers easily predictable. Your 
    personal information, such as resident registration numbers, legal alien registration numbers, bank 
    account numbers and credit card numbers, will be, after encrypted by safe password algorithms, kept 
    and managed.
    
    B. Anti-hacking Measures
    To prevent leak of your personal information as a result of intrusion to our information and 
    communications networks, such as hacking, we operate intrusion detection and firewall systems for 24 
    hours a day. To prevent an intrusion, all of our intrusion detection and firewall systems have duplex 
    configuration, and for secure transmission on networks, sensitive personal information in transit is 
    protected through encryption etc..
    
    C. Minimization and Training of Personal Information Managers
    We limit the number of our employees who handle personal information to the minimum level necessary 
    and impress on them the importance of protection of personal data through managerial safeguards, 
    including but not limited to their training.
    
    D. Operation of a Separate Department particularly for the Protection of Personal Information
    For the efficient protection of personal information, we operate a separate department particularly 
    for the protection of personal information. Further we exert our efforts to correct any problem, 
    if found, through checking items to comply with under this Policy and whether our personal 
    information managers are in compliance with the Policy.
    
    10. Privacy Officer
    
    We exert our best efforts to help you use our services safely. You can report any complaint on 
    privacy issues in relation to the use of our services, to our privacy officer or a separate 
    department in charge of protection of personal information, and we will respond to your reports 
    promptly and with sincerity.
    Protection of Personal Information
    
    Privacy Officer Name: [Samwoo, Lee]
    Title: [CEO];
    Email:help@testerkorea.com
    Tel No.: +82-31-978-0090
    
    If any other reporting or counseling is required in relation to infringement of personal 
    information, please contact the following institutions for inquiry.
    
    KISA (Korea Internet & Security Agency) :
    Tel No.: (with no preceding number) 118
    URL : http://www.118.or.kr
    
    KAIT (Korea Association of Information and Telecommunication) :
    Tel No.: 02-580-0533~4
    URL : http://www.eprivacy.or.kr
    
    SPO (Supreme Prosecutor’s Office Republic of Korea) :
    Tel No.: 02-3480-2000
    URL : http://www.spo.go.kr 
    
    CTRC (Cyber Terror Response Center) : 
    Tel No.: 02-393-9112
    URL : http://www.ctrc.go.kr
    
    11. Obligation of Notification
    
    This Policy may be amended pursuant to the government’s policy or out of necessity of the Company.
    Any addition, deletion or revision of this Policy will be notified in advance on our homepage or by 
    email at least 7 days prior to the effective date, and if it is difficult to give prior notification, 
    it will be notified subject to availability without delay; provided that if any material term (i.e., 
    the purpose of collection and use of personal information, the third party to which personal information 
    will be provided, etc.) is added, deleted or revised, such addition, deletion or revision will be 
    notified in advance at least 30 days prior to the effective date that the Policy as amended will take 
    effect 30 days from the date of notification. In addition, in case where any content to which requires 
    us to obtain from you a separate consent to any consent item (i.e., the collection and use of personal 
    information, provision of personal information to a third party, etc.) under applicable law or 
    regulation (including without limitation, the IC Network Act, etc.) is added or changed, we will obtain 
    a separate consent from you pursuant to the applicable law or regulation.
    
    Date of Notification: Jun 1, 2015
    
    Effective Date: Jun 1, 2015

    개인정보취급방침
    01. 개인정보의 수집·이용
    
    가. 회사가 개인정보를 수집하는 목적은 이용자의 신분과 서비스 이용의사를 확인하여 최적화되고 맞춤화된 서비스를 제공하기 위함입니다. 회사는 최초 회원가입 시 서비스 제공을 원활하게 하기 위해 필요한 최소한의 정보만을 수집하고 있으며 회사가 제공하는 서비스 이용에 따른 대금결제, 물품배송 및 환불 등에 필요한 정보를 추가로 수집할 수 있습니다.
    
    나. 회사는 개인정보를 수집·이용목적 이외에 다른 용도로 이를 이용하거나 이용자의 동의 없이 제3자에게 이를 제공하지 않습니다.
    
    다. 회사는 다음과 같은 목적으로 개인정보를 수집하여 이용할 수 있습니다. 다만, 전자상거래 등에서의 소비자보호에 관한 법률, 국세기본법, 전자금융거래법 등 관련법령에 따라 주민등록번호 및 은행계좌번호의 수집·보관이 불가피한 경우나, 휴대폰 소액결제 등 요금정산을 위하여 이동전화번호정보의 수집·보관이 불가피한 경우에는 이용자에게 고지하여 해당 정보를 수집할 수 있습니다.
    1) 이름, 이메일 주소(로그인 아이디), 이동전화번호, 주소, 수취인 이메일 : 거래의 원활한 진행, 본인의사의 확인, 불만처리, 새로운 상품, 서비스 정보와 고지사항의 안내, 회원의 서비스 이용 통계 및 설문 등
    2) 부가서비스 및 맞춤식 서비스 이용 또는 이벤트 응모 과정에서 해당 서비스의 이용자에 한해서 아래와 같은 정보가 수집될 수 있습니다.
    - 개인정보 추가 수집에 대해 동의를 받는 경우
    3) 기타 서비스 이용과정이나 사업처리 과정에서 아래와 같은 정보들이 자동으로 생성되어 수집될 수 있습니다.
    - IP Address, 방문일시, 서비스 이용 기록 : 부정 이용 방지, 비인가 사용 방지, 신규 서비스 개발 및 맞춤서비스 제공 등
    
    라. 회사는 이용자의 개인정보를 수집할 경우 반드시 이용자의 동의를 얻어 수집하며, 이용자의 기본적 인권을 침해할 우려가 있는 인종, 출신지, 본적지, 사상, 정치적 성향, 범죄기록, 건강상태 등의 정보는 이용자의 동의 또는 법령의 규정에 의한 경우 이외에는 수집하지 않습니다.
    
    마. 회사는 회원 가입을 만 14세 이상인 경우에 가능하도록 하며 개인정보의 수집·이용에 법정대리인의 동의가 필요한 만 14세 미만 아동의 개인정보는 원칙적으로 수집하지 않습니다. 단, 법정대리인의 동의를 얻은 경우에는 만 14세 미만 이용자의 개인정보를 수집·이용할 수 있습니다.
    
    바. 회사는 다음과 같은 방법으로 개인정보를 수집할 수 있습니다.
    1) 홈페이지, 서면, 팩스, 전화, 고객센터 문의하기, 이벤트 응모
    2) 생성정보 수집 툴을 통한 자동 수집
    
    02. 개인정보 제3자 제공
    
    가. 회사는 이용자들의 개인정보를 「개인정보의 수집·이용」에서 고지한 범위 내에서 사용하며, 이용자의 사전 동의 없이 동 범위를 초과하여 이용하거나 원칙적으로 이용자의 개인정보를 제3자에게 제공하지 않습니다. 다만, 아래의 경우에는 예외로 합니다.
    1) 이용자들이 사전에 공개 또는 제3자 제공에 동의한 경우
    2) 법령의 규정에 의거하거나, 수사, 조사 목적으로 법령에 정해진 절차와 방법에 따라 수사기관 및 감독당국의 요구가 있는 경우
    
    나. 회사가 제공하는 서비스를 통하여 주문 및 결제가 이루어진 경우 상담 등 거래 당사자간 원활한 의사소통 및 배송 등 거래이행을 위하여 관련된 정보를 필요한 범위 내에서 거래 당사자에게 제공합니다.
    
    다. 그 밖에 개인정보 제3자제공이 필요한 경우에는 이용자의 동의를 얻는 등 합당한 절차를 통하여 제3자에게 개인정보를 제공할 수 있습니다.
    
    03. 개인정보의 취급위탁
    
    가. 회사는 원활하고 향상된 서비스를 위하여 개인정보 취급을 타인에게 위탁할 수 있습니다.
    
    나. 회사는 개인정보의 처리와 관련하여 아래와 같이 업무를 위탁하고 있으며, 관계법령에 따라 위탁 계약 시 개인정보가 안전하게 관리될 수 있도록 필요한 조치를 하고 있습니다. 또한 위탁처리하는 정보는 원활한 서비스를 제공하기 위하여 필요한 최소한의 정보에 국한됩니다.
    수탁업체	위탁업무내용
    우체국	해외 배송
    베어스 항공	해외 배송
    DHL	해외 배송
    
    04. 이용자 개인정보의 보유 ： 이용기간 및 파기
    
    회사는 이용자의 개인정보를 원칙적으로 고지 및 약정한 기간 동안 보유 및 이용하며 개인정보의 수집 및 이용목적이 달성되면 지체 없이 파기합니다. 단, 다음의 정보에 대해서는 아래의 이유로 명시한 기간 동안 보존합니다
    
    가. 관련법령 및 회사 방침에 의한 정보보유 사유
    상법 등 관계법령의 규정에 의하여 보존할 필요가 있는 경우 법령에서 규정한 일정한 기간 동안 이용자 개인정보를 보관합니다. 이 경우 회사는 보관하는 정보를 그 보관의 목적으로만 이용하며 보존기간은 아래와 같습니다.
    1) 계약 또는 청약철회 등에 관한 기록
    보존 이유 : 전자상거래 등에서의 소비자보호에 관한 법률 제6조 및 시행령 제6조
    보존 기간 : 5년
    2) 대금결제 및 재화 등의 공급에 관한 기록
    보존 이유 : 전자상거래 등에서의 소비자보호에 관한 법률 제6조 및 시행령 제6조
    보존 기간 : 5년
    3) 소비자의 불만 또는 분쟁처리에 관한 기록
    보존 이유 : 전자상거래 등에서의 소비자보호에 관한 법률 제6조 및 시행령 제6조
    보존 기간 : 3년
    4) 접속에 관한 기록
    보존 이유 : 통신비밀보호법 제15조의2 및 시행령 제41조
    보존기간 : 3개월
    5) 부정거래기록
    보존 이유 : 부정거래의 배제
    보존 기간 : 1년
    
    나. 수집된 개인정보의 보유·이용기간은 서비스이용계약체결(회원가입)시부터 서비스이용계약해지(탈퇴신청, 직권탈퇴 포함)입니다. 또한 동의 해지 시 회사는 이용자의 개인정보를 상기 명시한 정보보유 사유에 따라 일정 기간 저장하는 자료를 제외하고는 지체 없이 파기하며 개인정보취급이 제3자에게 위탁된 경우에는 수탁자에게도 파기하도록 지시합니다.
    
    05. 쿠키(Cookie)의 운용 및 거부
    
    가. 쿠키의 사용 목적
    1) 회사는 개인 맞춤 서비스를 제공하기 위해서 이용자에 대한 정보를 저장하고 수시로 불러오는 '쿠키(cookie)'를 사용합니다. 쿠키는 웹사이트 서버가 이용자의 브라우저에게 전송하는 소량의 정보로서 이용자 컴퓨터의 하드디스크에 저장됩니다.
    2) 회사는 쿠키의 사용을 통해서만 가능한 특정된 맞춤형 서비스를 제공할 수 있습니다.
    3) 회사는 회원을 식별하고 회원의 로그인 상태를 유지하기 위해 쿠키를 사용할 수 있습니다.
    
    나. 쿠키의 설치/운용 및 거부
    1) 이용자는 쿠키 설치에 대한 선택권을 가지고 있습니다. 따라서 이용자는 웹브라우저에서 옵션을 조정함으로써 모든 쿠키를 허용/거부하거나, 쿠키가 저장될 때마다 확인을 거치도록 할 수 있습니다.
    - 쿠키 설치 허용 여부를 지정하는 방법(Internet Explorer의 경우)은 다음과 같습니다.
    [도구] 메뉴에서 [인터넷 옵션]을 선택합니다.
    [개인정보 탭]을 클릭합니다.
    [개인정보취급 수준]을 설정하시면 됩니다.
    
    2) 쿠키의 저장을 거부할 경우에는 개인 맞춤서비스 등 회사가 제공하는 일부 서비스는 이용이 어려울 수 있습니다.
    
    06. 이용자의 권리
    
    가. 이용자는 언제든지 테스터코리아 사이트의 “정보수정”을 통하여 회원님의 개인정보를 열람, 정정 처리하실 수 있으며, 당사의 개인정보관리책임자에게 전자우편 또는 서면으로 요청하신 경우열람, 정정, 삭제처리 해드리겠습니다. 기타 법률에 따라 정정 또는 삭제가 금지되거나 제한되어 있는 경우에는 해당 처리가 제한될 수 있습니다. 또한 개인정보 오류에 대한 정정 요청한 경우에는 다른 법률에 따라 개인정보의 제공을 요청 받는 경우가 아닌 한 정정을 완료하기 전까지 당해 개인정보를 이용 또는 제공하지 않습니다, 만약 잘못된 개인정보를 이미 제공한 경우에는 정정 처리 결과를 제 3자에게 통지하여 정정이 이루어지도록 하겠습니다.
    
    나. 이용자는 언제든지 테스터코리아 사이트의 개인정보에 대하여 처리의 정지를 요구 할 수 있습니다. 다만 아래의 경우에 해당하는 경우 처리정지 요구를 거절할 수 있습니다.
    1) 법률에 특별한 규정이 있거나 법령상 의무를 준수하기 위하여 불가피한 경우
    2) 다른 사람의 생명·신체를 해할 우려가 있거나 다른 사람의 재산과 그 밖의 이익을 부당하게 침해할 우려가 있는 경우
    3) 개인정보를 처리하지 아니하면 정보주체와 약정한 서비스를 제공하지 못하는 등 계약의 이행이 곤란한 경우로서 정보주체가 그 계약의 해지 의사를 명확하게 밝히지 아니한 경우
    
    다. 회원가입 등을 통해 개인정보의 수집·이용·제공에 대해 회원님께서 동의하신 내용을 언제든지 철회할 수 있습니다. 동의철회는 회사 사이트 내 “회원 탈퇴 신청”을 클릭하거나 개인정보관리책임자에게 서면, 전화, 이메일 등으로 연락하시면 지체 없이 개인정보의 삭제 등 필요한 조치를 하겠습니다. 다만 법률 또는 약관의 규정에 따라 회사가 회원님의 개인정보를 보존하여야 하는 경우에는 해당 처리가 제한될 수 있습니다. 이 경우 회원님은 본인 식별을 위하여 반드시 회원아이디(ID)와 본인확인 식별정보를 밝히셔야 하며, 철회로 인해 서비스에 다소 제약이 있거나 일부 서비스를 이용하지 못하실 수 있습니다
    
    07. 이용자의 의무
    
    이용자는 자신의 개인정보를 보호할 의무가 있으며, 회사의 귀책사유가 없이 ID, 비밀번호, 접근매체 등의 양도·대여·분실이나 로그인 상태에서 이석 등 이용자 본인의 부주의나 브라우저 취약점, 관계법령에 의한 보안조치로 차단할 수 없는 방법이나 기술을 사용한 해킹 등 회사가 상당한 주의에도 불구하고 통제할 수 없는 인터넷 상의 문제 등으로 개인정보가 유출되어 발생한 문제에 대해 회사는 일체의 책임을 지지 않습니다.
    
    가. 이용자는 자신의 개인정보를 최신의 상태로 유지해야 하며, 이용자의 부정확한 정보 입력으로 발생하는 문제의 책임은 이용자 자신에게 있습니다.
    
    나. 이용자는 아이디, 비밀번호 등에 대해 보안을 유지할 책임이 있으며 제3자에게 이를 양도하거나 대여할 수 없습니다. 이용자는 회사의 개인정보보호정책에 따라 보안을 위해 비밀번호의 주기적 변경에 협조할 의무가 있습니다.
    
    다. 이용자는 회사의 서비스를 이용한 후에는 반드시 로그인 계정을 종료하고 웹 브라우저 프로그램을 종료해야 합니다.
    
    라. 이용자는 "정보 통신망 이용촉진 및 정보보호 등에 관한 법률", “개인정보보호법”, "주민등록법" 등 기타 개인정보에 관한 법률을 준수하여야 합니다.
    
    08. 링크 사이트에 대한 책임
    
    회사는 이용자에게 다른 웹사이트에 대한 링크를 제공할 수 있습니다. 다만, 링크되어 있는 웹사이트들이 개인정보를 수집하는 행위에 대해서는 본 "개인정보취급방침"이 적용되지 않습니다.
    
    09. 개인정보의 기술적／관리적 보호 대책
    
    회사는 이용자들의 개인정보를 취급함에 있어 개인정보가 분실, 도난, 누출, 변조 또는 훼손되지 않도록 안전성 확보를 위하여 다음과 같은 기술적/관리적 보호대책을 강구하고 있습니다.
    
    가. 개인정보의 암호화
    이용자의 비밀번호는 일방향 암호화하여 저장 및 관리되고 있으며, 개인정보의 확인 및 변경은 비밀번호를 알고 있는 본인에 의해서만 가능합니다. 비밀번호는 이용자의 생일, 전화번호 등 타인이 추측하기 쉬운 숫자 등을 이용하지 않도록 비밀번호 생성규칙을 수립하여 적용하고 있습니다. 주민등록번호, 외국인 등록번호, 은행계좌번호 및 신용카드번호 등의 개인정보는 안전한 암호 알고리즘으로 암호화되어 저장 및 관리되고 있습니다.
    
    나. 해킹 등에 대비한 대책
    회사는 해킹 등 회사 정보통신망 침입에 의해 이용자의 개인정보가 유출되는 것을 방지하기 위해 침입탐지 및 침입차단 시스템을 24시간 가동하고 있습니다. 만일의 사태에 대비하여 모든 침입탐지 시스템과 침입차단 시스템은 이중화로 구성하여 운영하고 있으며, 민감한 개인정보는 암호화 통신 등을 통하여 네트워크상에서 개인정보를 안전하게 전송할 수 있도록 하고 있습니다.
    
    다. 개인정보 취급자의 최소화 및 교육
    회사는 회사의 개인정보 취급자를 최소한으로 제한하며, 개인정보 취급자에 대한 교육 등 관리적 조치를 통해 개인정보보호의 중요성을 인식시키고 있습니다.
    
    라. 개인정보보호 전담부서의 운영
    회사는 개인정보의 효율적 보호를 위해 개인정보보호전담부서를 운영하고 있으며, 개인정보취급방침의 이행사항 및 개인정보 취급자의 준수여부를 확인하여 문제가 발견될 경우 즉시 수정할 수 있도록 노력하고 있습니다.
    
    10. 개인정보관리책임자
    
    회사는 이용자가 회사의 서비스를 안전하게 이용할 수 있도록 최선을 다하고 있습니다. 이용자는 회사의 서비스 이용과 관련한 모든 개인정보보호 민원을 개인정보관리책임자 또는 전담부서로 신고하실 수 있으며, 회사는 이용자의 신고사항에 대해 신속하고 성실하게 답변해드리고 있습니다.
    
    개인정보관리 책임자
    성명 : 이삼우
    직위 : 대표
        전자우편 : tech@testerkorea.com
        전화번호 : +82-31-978-0090

    기타 개인정보침해에 대한 신고 또는 상담이 필요하신 경우에는 아래 기관으로 문의하시기 바랍니다.
    
    개인정보침해신고센터
    전화 : (국번없이)118
    URL : http://www.118.or.kr
    
    정보보호마크인증위원회
        전화 : 02-550-9531~2
        URL : http://www.eprivacy.or.kr
    
    대검찰청 첨단범죄수사센터
        전화 : 02-3480-2000
        URL : http://www.spo.go.kr
    
    경찰청 사이버테러대응센터
        전화 : 02-393-9112
        URL : http://www.ctrc.go.kr
    
    11. 고지의 의무
    
    현 개인정보취급방침은 정부의 정책 또는 회사의 필요에 의하여 변경될 수 있으며 내용의 추가 및 삭제, 수정이 있을 시에는 시행 7일 전에 홈페이지 또는 이메일을 통해 사전 공지하며 사전 공지가 곤란한 경우 지체 없이 공지하며, 이 정책은 공지한 날로부터 시행됩니다. . 다만, 개인정보의 수집·이용 목적, 제3자 제공대상 등 중요한 사항이 추가 및 삭제, 수정되는 경우에는 30일 전에 사전 공지하고, 30일이 경과된 후에 시행됩니다. 또한 당사는 개인정보의 수집 및 활용, 제3자 제공 등 정보통신망 이용촉진 및 정보보호 등에 관한 법률 등 관련법령에 따라 고객의 별도 동의가 필요한 사항과 관련된 내용이 추가, 변경되는 경우에는 관련 법령에 따른 고객의 별도 동의를 받습니다.
    
    공고일자 : 2015년 6월 1일
    
    시행일자 : 2015년 6월 1일
    
    고객 개인정보보호와 관련하여 의견이나 불만이 있으시면 개인정보보호책임자에게 문의하여 주십시오. 신속하고 정확하게 처리해 드리도록 하겠습니다.
